Hello there!
أهلاً بك!
You’re back with me, Kade, once again!
لقد عدت معي ، كادي ، مرة أخرى!
Today, I’m going to take you guys to tour my house.
اليوم ، سأصطحبكم يا رفاق للقيام بجولة في منزلي.
Coz many have been asking me.
لقد سألني الكثير من Coz.
“Why are you surrounded by so many men?”
"لماذا أنت محاط بالعديد من الرجال؟"
Actually, they are all my beloved buddies.
في الواقع ، إنهم جميعًا رفاقي المحبوبين.
Let’s start with umm…
لنبدأ بأم ...
The first dude here.
المتأنق الأول هنا.
Frank.
صريح.
With this one, we could actually die for each other.
مع هذا ، يمكننا في الواقع أن نموت من أجل بعضنا البعض.
Despite how he looks.
على الرغم من مظهره.
He’s a bakery chef who graduated from France.
إنه طاهي مخبوزات تخرج من فرنسا.
He has recently been relocated back here.
لقد تم نقله مؤخرًا إلى هنا.
That’s why I invited him to stay over here, too.
لهذا السبب دعوته للبقاء هنا أيضًا.
Ahh, he has some strange habits also.
آه ، لديه بعض العادات الغريبة أيضًا.
Look at him.
انظر اليه.
Such a perfectionist.
هذا منشد الكمال.
Don’t ever let him spot any grain of dust in his kitchen.
لا تدعه يكتشف أي ذرة من الغبار في مطبخه.
He will be extremely pissed.
سيكون غاضبًا للغاية.
If you don’t believe me, come check this out.
إذا كنت لا تصدقني ، تعال لتفقد هذا.
What are you making today, Cheft?
ماذا تصنع اليوم يا شيفت؟
What’s wrong with you?!
ما مشكلتك؟!
Are you really my mate, dude?
هل أنت حقا رفيقي يا صاح؟
Let’s move on to the next one.
دعنا ننتقل إلى المرحلة التالية.
Oh, always at the perfect timing.
أوه ، دائمًا في التوقيت المثالي.
An artistic, fashionist and professional photographer.
مصور فني ، مصمم أزياء ومحترف.
He looks the most grown up under this roof.
يبدو أنه الأكثر كبرًا تحت هذا السقف.
This guy is Big.
هذا الرجل كبير.
Sometimes he also turns into model himself.
في بعض الأحيان يتحول أيضًا إلى نموذج.
That’s because he’s this good-looking.
هذا لأنه هذا حسن المظهر.
How could he stay behind the camera only?
كيف يمكنه البقاء خلف الكاميرا فقط؟
Actually.. he is quite perfect.
في الواقع .. إنه مثالي تمامًا.
Except that…
ماعادا هذا…
He is that kind of person that needs to drink black coffee with orange before working.
إنه ذلك النوع من الأشخاص الذين يحتاجون إلى شرب القهوة السوداء بالبرتقال قبل العمل.
Isn’t it true, Big?
أليس هذا صحيحًا يا كبير؟
Stop messing around and get out, you! I have to take some photos here.
توقف عن العبث واخرج ، أنت!  لا بد لي من التقاط بعض الصور هنا.
I got scolded. Let’s get outta here.
لقد وبخت.  هيا بنا من هنا.
Meh…
مه…
When he took photos of me, he was never this focused.
عندما التقط صوراً لي ، لم يكن بهذا التركيز أبدًا.
Ohhh…
أوه ...
So much touch-up right there, Mr. Big.
الكثير من اللمسات هناك ، سيد بيج.
What are you doing standing over there?
ماذا تفعل واقف هناك؟
Yea, you, get out, I have to take photos.
أجل ، أخرجي ، عليّ أن ألتقط الصور.
Here, take photos of my plant, too, then.
هنا ، التقط صورًا لمصنعي أيضًا ، إذن.
I thought they were gonna fight.
اعتقدت أنهم سيقاتلون.
I forgot to mention one more thing.
لقد نسيت أن أذكر شيئًا آخر.
Big has a younger twin brother named Boss.
لدى Big شقيق توأم أصغر اسمه Boss.
But they don’t get along well, as you can see.
لكنهم لا يتوافقون بشكل جيد ، كما ترون.
I kinda get Boss actually.
أنا أحصل على بوس في الواقع كيندا.
He has been compared with since he was a kid.
تمت مقارنته به منذ أن كان طفلاً.
Boss loves freedom.
الزعيم يحب الحرية.
Loves to travel, and loves plants.
يحب السفر ويحب النباتات.
His main job is to keep on making game broadcasting.
وظيفته الرئيسية هي الاستمرار في بث اللعبة.
And his parents are not so happy about that.
ووالديه ليسوا سعداء بذلك.
The main reason why these two came to live here in my house is because.
السبب الرئيسي وراء قدوم هذين الشخصين للعيش هنا في منزلي هو ذلك.
They are my cousins.
هم أبناء عمي.
Now you guys got to know all of my roommates.
الآن تعرفتم يا رفاق على جميع زملائي في السكن.
Let me introduce you to the most handsome guy of this house.
اسمحوا لي أن أقدم لكم الرجل الأكثر وسامة في هذا المنزل.
Who else is it going to be?
من غيره سيكون؟
Me, Kade!
أنا ، كادي!
I am handsome, playful and intelligent.
أنا وسيم ومرحة وذكية.
I am the most perfect man of this house.
أنا أفضل رجل في هذا المنزل.
Any of you girls interested.
أي من الفتيات مهتمات.
You can comment in the clip to chat with me.
يمكنك التعليق في المقطع للدردشة معي.
In the next clip, what will I review or where will I take you to?
في المقطع التالي ، ماذا سأراجع أو إلى أين سأأخذك؟
Don’t forget to turn on the notification and subscribe to my channel.
لا تنس تشغيل الإشعار والاشتراك في قناتي.
Hi there, Gibsy!
مرحبًا يا جبسي!
For you, Gibsy, I am free every night.
من أجلك يا جبسي أنا حرة كل ليلة.
Sure, see you.
بالتأكيد ، أراك.
How should I dress up?
كيف أرتدي ملابسي؟
Are you rearranging the garden?
هل تعيد ترتيب الحديقة؟
Yea, I got some good stuff.
نعم ، لدي بعض الأشياء الجيدة.
This rose is really rare in Thailand.
هذه الوردة نادرة حقًا في تايلاند.
You are expert about flowers.
أنت خبير في الزهور.
I have to hurry to grow it up.
لا بد لي من الإسراع لتنمو.
Or else suddenly, someone moves in as our new neighbor.
أو فجأة ، ينتقل شخص ما كجار جديد لنا.
And then has the same problem as the previous one again.
ومن ثم لديه نفس المشكلة السابقة مرة أخرى.
Oh true. I heard that someone is moving into our village.
يا صحيح.  سمعت أن شخصًا ما ينتقل إلى قريتنا.
But if it’s a pretty and hot girl, I am totally fine with that.
ولكن إذا كانت فتاة جميلة وساخنة ، فأنا بخير تمامًا مع ذلك.
Give it a break. You are too much about girls.
امنحها استراحة.  أنت تهتم كثيرا بالفتيات.
You may have unwanted encounter among them girls just like Kade did.
قد يكون لديك لقاء غير مرغوب فيه بينهم فتيات مثلما فعلت كادي.
Kade always has his guards down when it comes to girls.
كادي دائمًا ما يحافظ على حراسه عندما يتعلق الأمر بالفتيات.
Just let him be.
فقط دعه يكون.
Here, a cake of new recipe, help me try it, please.
هنا ، كعكة من وصفة جديدة ، ساعدني في تجربتها من فضلك.
Wow, lookin’ so yummy.
واو ، تبدو لذيذة للغاية.
Less-sweet recipe.
وصفة أقل حلاوة.
Aha, out of my way, guys.
آها ، بعيدًا عن طريقي يا رفاق.
I was thinking of going out.
كنت أفكر في الخروج.
Where are you going hunting?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب للصيد؟
Prestigious casanova.
كازانوفا المرموقة.
Huh, be careful, you.
هاه ، كن حذرا ، أنت.
Girls nowadays are not that stupid anymore.
الفتيات في الوقت الحاضر ليسوا بهذا الغباء بعد الآن.
Lessons are there to learn and to help develop yourself or not.
الدروس موجودة لتتعلم وتساعد على تطوير نفسك أم لا.
This one is rare item.
هذا عنصر نادر.
Her eyes are even sweeter than my dessert.
عيناها أحلى من الحلوى.
Gosh, how I wanna get to know her!
يا إلهي ، كيف أريد التعرف عليها!
Hey Preen, how did you get here?
مرحبًا برين ، كيف أتيت إلى هنا؟
Hey, Big!
يا كبير!
How come you are around here?
كيف جئت هنا؟
This here is my house. It’s just I forgot something, so I came back for it.
هذا هو بيتي.  لقد نسيت شيئًا فقط ، لذا عدت من أجله.
Mhmm..
أمم..
We haven’t seen each other in such long time.
لم نر بعضنا البعض منذ وقت طويل.
A long time indeed.
لقد مضى وقت طويل بالفعل.
I miss you, Big.
اشتقت لك يا كبير.
Big!!
كبير!!
Mr. Big!
سيد كبير!
Well, this morning, I saw that you were...
حسنًا ، هذا الصباح ، رأيت أنك ...
Hugging with the new girl that just moved in.
المعانقة مع الفتاة الجديدة التي انتقلت للتو.
Here is a thing..
هنا شيء ..
A four-day mission with which we are going to hit on Preen.
مهمة لمدة أربعة أيام سنضرب بها برين.